<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.liquidshell.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license> GPL-3.0 </project_license>
  <name>liquidshell</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">liquidshell</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">liquidshell</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">liquidshell</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">liquidshell</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">liquidshell</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">liquidshell</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">liquidshell</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">liquidshell</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">liquidshell</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">liquidshell</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">liquidshell</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">liquidshell</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">liquidshell</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">liquidshell</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Liquid-skal</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">liquidshell</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxliquidshellxx</name>
  <summary> liquidshell is an alternative to plasmashell </summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">El liquidshell és una alternativa al plasmashell</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">El liquidshell és una alternativa al plasmashell</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">liquidshell ist eine Alternative zu plasmashell</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">liquidshell is an alternative to plasmashell</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">liquidshell es una alternativa a plasmashell</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">liquidshell on plasmashellin vaihtoehto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">liquidshell é unha alternativa a plasmashell</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">liquidshell adalah sebuah alternatif untuk plasmashell</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">liquidshell è un'alternativa a plasmashell</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">liquidshell is een alternatief voor plasmashell</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">liquidshell jest alternatywą dla plasmashell</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">O 'liquidshell' é uma alternativa ao 'plasmashell'</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">liquidshell je alternatíva pre plasmashell</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Liquid-skal är ett alternativ till Plasma-skal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">liquidshell є альтернативою оболонки Плазми</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxliquidshell is an alternative to plasmashellxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>liquidshell is an alternative to plasmashell</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El liquidshell és una alternativa al plasmashell</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El liquidshell és una alternativa al plasmashell</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">liquidshell ist eine Alternative zu plasmashell</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">liquidshell is an alternative to plasmashell</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">liquidshell es una alternativa a plasmashell</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">liquidshell on plasmashellin vaihtoehto</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">liquidshell é unha alternativa a plasmashell</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">liquidshell adalah sebuah alternatif untuk plasmashell</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">liquidshell è un'alternativa a plasmashell</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">liquidshell is een alternatief voor plasmashell</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">liquidshell jest alternatywą dla plasmashell</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O 'liquidshell' é uma alternativa ao 'plasmashell'</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">liquidshell je alternatíva pre plasmashell</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Liquid-skal är ett alternativ till Plasma-skal</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">liquidshell є альтернативою оболонки Плазми</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxliquidshell is an alternative to plasmashellxx</p>
    <p>It does not use QtQuick but instead relies on QtWidgets,
       therefore no hardware graphics acceleration is needed.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">No usa el QtQuick, sinó que es basa en els QtWidgets, per tant, no cal acceleració gràfica per maquinari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">No usa el QtQuick, sinó que es basa en els QtWidgets, per tant, no cal acceleració gràfica per maquinari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">It does not use QtQuick but instead relies on QtWidgets, therefore no hardware graphics acceleration is needed.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Se ei käytä QtQuickiä vaan luottaa QtWidgetsiin, joten se ei vaadi laitteistokiihdytystä.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Non usa QtQuick senón QtWidgets, polo que non require aceleración gráfica por hardware.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Ini tidaklah menggunakan QtQuick tapi alih-alih bergantung pada QtWidgets, yang mana tidak diperlukannya akselerasi grafik hardware.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Non usa QtQuick ma fa invece affidamento su QtWidgets, quindi non necessita di accelerazione grafica hardware.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het gebruikt geen QtQuick maar hangt in plaats daarvan af van QtWidgets, er is daarom geen hardware grafische versnelling nodig.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Zamiast używać QtQuick używa QtWidgets, więc nie jest wymagane żande sprzętowe przyspieszenie grafiki.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Não usa o QtQuick mas baseia-se sim no QtWidgets, pelo que não é necessária nenhuma aceleração gráfica por 'hardware'.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Det använder inte QtQuick, utan förlitar sig istället på QtWidgets. Därför behövs ingen grafikacceleration i hårdvara.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Не використовує QtQuick, а лише QtWidgets, тому не потрібне апаратне прискорення виведення графіки</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxIt does not use QtQuick but instead relies on QtWidgets, therefore no hardware graphics acceleration is needed.xx</p>
    <p>Main Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques principals:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques principals:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Hlavní vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Kernfunktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Main Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funciones principales:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Keskeiset ominaisuudet:</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidades principais:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Fitur Utama:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità principali:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Hoofdkenmerken:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Główne możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades Principais:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Hlavné funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Huvudfunktionalitet:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Основні можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxMain Features:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Wallpaper per virtual desktop</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Fons de pantalla per a l'escriptori virtual</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Fons de pantalla per a l'escriptori virtual</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Hintergrundbild je virtueller Arbeitsfläche</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Wallpaper per virtual desktop</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Fondo de pantalla por escritorio virtual</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Virtuaalityöpöydittäiset taustakuvat</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Fondo de escritorio por escritorio virtual.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Wallpaper tiap desktop virtual</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Sfondo per desktop virtuali</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Achtergrondafbeelding per virtueel bureaublad</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Tapeta na wirtualny pulpit</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Papel de parede por ecrã virtual</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Skrivbordsunderlägg per virtuellt skrivbord</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Різні зображення тла для різних віртуальних стільниць</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxWallpaper per virtual desktopxx</li>
      <li>No animations, no CPU hogging, low Memory footprint</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">No hi ha animacions, sense acaparar la CPU, consum baix de la memòria</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">No hi ha animacions, sense acaparar la CPU, consum baix de la memòria</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">No animations, no CPU hogging, low Memory footprint</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Ei animointeja tai suorittimen rohmuamista; vähäinen muistinkulutus</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Sen animacións, cun uso baixo de CPU e memoria.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Tidak ada animasi, tidak ada kelokan CPU, lemahnya jejak Memori</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Nessuna animazione, nessun uso intensivo della CPU, uso limitato della memoria</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Geen animaties, geen CPU belasting, lage voetafdruk op geheugen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Brak animacji, brak zapychania CPU, małe wykorzystanie pamięci</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Sem animações, sem bloqueios do CPU, pouco consumo de memória</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Inga animeringar, ingen beslagtagning av processorn, liten minnesanvändning</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Немає анімацій, зайвого споживання часу процесора, менше споживання пам'яті</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxNo animations, no CPU hogging, low Memory footprintxx</li>
      <li>Instant startup</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Inici instantani</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Inici instantani</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Okamžité spuštění</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Instant startup</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Inicio instantáneo</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Välitön käynnistys</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Inicio instantáneo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Pemulaian sekejap</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Avvio istantaneo</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Onmiddellijk opgestart</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Natychmiastowe uruchamianie</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Arranque instantâneo</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Rýchle spustenie</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Omedelbar start</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Миттєвий запуск</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxInstant startupxx</li>
      <li>No use of activities</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">No empra les activitats</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">No empra les activitats</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Aktivitäten werden nicht verwendet</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">No use of activities</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">No se usan las actividades</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Ei käytä aktiviteetteja</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Sen actividades.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Tidak ada penggunaan aktivitas</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Nessun uso delle attività</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Geen gebruik van activiteiten</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Nie używa aktywności</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Não usa as actividades</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Žiadne použitie aktívít</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Ingen användning av aktiviteter</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Не використовуються простори дій</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxNo use of activitiesxx</li>
      <li>QtWidgets based, therefore follows widget style from systemsettings</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Està basat en els QtWidgets, per tant, segueix l'estil dels estris indicat per l'arranjament del sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Està basat en els QtWidgets, per tant, segueix l'estil dels estris indicat per l'arranjament del sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">QtWidgets based, therefore follows widget style from systemsettings</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Perustuu QtWidgetsiin, joten noudattaa järjestelmäasetusten käyttöliittymäalkiotyyliä</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Baseado en QtWidgets, polo que usa o estilo de trebello definido na configuración do sistema.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Berdasarkan QtWidgets, yang mana mengikuti gaya widget dari systemsettings</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">È basato su QtWidgets, quindi segue lo stile degli oggetti delle Impostazioni di sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Gebaseerd op QtWidgets, volgt daarom widgetstijl uit systeeminstellingen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Oparte na QtWidgets, więc podąża za wyglądem z ustawień systemowych</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Baseado no QtWidgets, pelo que segue o estilo gráfico da Configuração do Sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Baserad på QtWidgets, och följer därför komponentstilen från systeminställningarna</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Засновано на QtWidgets, тому стиль віджетів повністю визначається «Системними параметрами»</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxQtWidgets based, therefore follows widget style from systemsettingsxx</li>
      <li>Icons are used from your globally defined icon theme from systemsettings</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Les icones s'usen des del tema d'icones definit globalment des de l'arranjament del sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Les icones s'usen des del tema d'icones definit globalment des de l'arranjament del sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Icons are used from your globally defined icon theme from systemsettings</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Käyttää järjestelmäasetuksissa määritetyn yleisen kuvaketeeman kuvakkeita</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Usa as iconas do tema de iconas definido globalmente desde a configuración do sistema.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Ikon-ikon telah digunakan dari tema ikon yang ditentukan secara globalmu dari systemsettings</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Le icone usate sono quelle del tema di icone definito globalmente nelle Impostazioni di sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Pictogrammen worden gebruikt uit uw globaal gedefinieerd pictogramthema uit systeeminstellingen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Ikony są brane z globalnie określonego zestawu ikon w ustawieniach systemowych</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">São usados os ícones do seu tema de ícones definido a nível global na Configuração do Sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Ikoner kommer från det globalt definierade ikontemat i systeminställningarna</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Використання піктограм із загальної визначеної теми із «Системних параметрів»</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxIcons are used from your globally defined icon theme from systemsettingsxx</li>
      <li>Colors are used from your globally defined color theme from systemsettings</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Els colors s'usen des del tema de color definit globalment des de l'arranjament del sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Els colors s'usen des del tema de color definit globalment des de l'arranjament del sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Colours are used from your globally defined colour theme from systemsettings</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Käyttää järjestelmäasetuksissa määritettyjä yleisiä väriasetuksia</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Usa as cores do tema de cores definido globalmente desde a configuración do sistema.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Warna-warna telah digunakan dari tema warna yang ditentukan secara globalmu dari systemsettings</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">I colori usati sono quelli del tema di colori definito globalmente nelle Impostazioni di sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Kleuren worden gebruikt uit uw globaal gedefinieerd kleurenthema uit systeeminstellingen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Kolory są brane z globalnie określonego zestawu kolorów w ustawieniach systemowych</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">São usadas as cores do seu tema de cores definido a nível global na Configuração do Sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Färger kommer från det globalt definierade färgtemat i systeminställningarna</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Використання заданих на загальному рівні кольорів із «Системних параметрів»</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxColors are used from your globally defined color theme from systemsettingsxx</li>
      <li>Can additionally be styled with css by passing the commandline option -stylesheet filename.css (see included example stylesheet.css)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">També es pot dissenyar amb css passant l'opció de línia d'ordres «-stylesheet filename.css» (vegeu l'exemple inclòs a stylesheet.css)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">També es pot dissenyar amb css passant l'opció de línia d'ordres «-stylesheet filename.css» (vegeu l'exemple inclòs a stylesheet.css)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Can additionally be styled with css by passing the commandline option -stylesheet filename.css (see included example stylesheet.css)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tyyliä voi vielä CSS:llä muokata komentorivivalitsinta ”-stylesheet tiedosto.css” käyttäen (ks. esimerkkitiedostoa stylesheet.css)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">O seu estilo pode cambiarse a maiores con CSS mediante a opción -stylesheet ficheiro.css da liña de ordes (consulte o exemplo de stylesheet.css incluído).</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Bisa ditambah-tambah gaya dengan css lewat commandline opsi -stylesheet filename.css (lihatlah contoh yang disertakan stylesheet.css)</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Lo stile può inoltre essere reso mediante css, passando l'opzione di riga di comando -stylesheet nomefile.css (vedi l'esempio stylesheet.css incluso)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Kan extra worden gestijld met css door de optie op de opdrachtregel -stylesheet bestandsnaam.css (zie bijgevoegd voorbeeld stylesheet.css)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Możliwość uszczegółowienia wyglądu poprzez podanie opcji wiersza poleceń css -stylesheet filename.css (zobacz załączony przykład stylesheet.css)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Pode ser modificado o seu estilo gráfico com CSS se passar a opção da linha de comandos '-stylesheet ficheiro.css' (veja o 'stylesheet.css' incluída no exemplo)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kan dessutom formateras med CSS genom att ange kommandoradsväljaren -stylesheet filnamn.css (se det inkluderade exemplet stylesheet.css)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Додаткова зміна стилю за допомогою css, достатньо лише передати параметр командного рядка -stylesheet назва_файла.css (див. включений приклад stylesheet.css)</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCan additionally be styled with css by passing the commandline option -stylesheet filename.css (see included example stylesheet.css)xx</li>
      <li>uses existing KDE dialogs for most configurations, e.g. StartMenu, Virtual Desktops, Bluetooth, Network</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Usa els diàlegs del KDE existents per a la majoria de les configuracions, p. ex. Menú d'inici, Escriptoris virtuals, Bluetooth, Xarxa</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Usa els diàlegs del KDE existents per a la majoria de les configuracions, p. ex. Menú d'inici, Escriptoris virtuals, Bluetooth, Xarxa</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">uses existing KDE dialogues for most configurations, e.g. StartMenu, Virtual Desktops, Bluetooth, Network</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Käyttää useimmiten olemassa olevia KDE-valintaikkunoita, esim. käynnistysvalikko, virtuaalityöpöydät, Bluetooth, verkko</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Usa diálogos de KDE existente para a meirande parte da configuración, como o menú de inicio, os escritorios virtuais, Bluetooth ou a rede.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">menggunakan dialog KDE yang ada untuk beberapa konfigurasi, misal StartMenu, Virtual Desktops, Bluetooth, Network</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">usa per la maggior parte delle configurazioni le finestre esistenti di KDE, ad esempio il Menu Avvio, i desktop virtuali, il Bluetooth, la rete</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">gebruikt bestaande KDE dialogen voor de meeste configuraties, bijv. StartMenu, Virtuele bureaubladen, Bluetooth, Netwerk</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">używa istniejących okien dialogowych KDE w większości przypadków, np. menu start, pulpity wirtualne, Bluetooth, sieć</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">usa as janelas existentes no KDE para a maioria das configurações, p.ex., Menu Iniciar, Ecrãs Virtuais, Bluetooth, Rede</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Använder befintliga dialogrutor i KDE för de flesta inställningar, t.ex. startmeny, virtuella skrivbord, Blåtand, nätverk</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Використання наявних вікон KDE для більшості налаштувань, зокрема меню запуску, віртуальних стільниць, Bluetooth, мережі</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxuses existing KDE dialogs for most configurations, e.g. StartMenu, Virtual Desktops, Bluetooth, Networkxx</li>
      <li>One bottom DesktopPanel</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Un plafó d'escriptori a la part inferior</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Un plafó d'escriptori a la part inferior</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">One bottom DesktopPanel</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Yksi alhaalla oleva työpöytäpaneeli</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Un panel de escritorio na parte inferior.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Salahsatu bagian bawah DesktopPanel</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Un pannello desktop in basso</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Eén bureaubladpaneel onderaan</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Jeden panel pulpitu na dole</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Um único painel inferior</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">En skrivbordspanel längst ner</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Одна панель у нижній частині екрана</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxOne bottom DesktopPanelxx</li>
      <li>Desktop Applets</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Miniaplicacions de l'escriptori</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Miniaplicacions de l'escriptori</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Desktop Applets</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Miniaplicaciones de escritorio</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Työpöytäsovelmat</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Trebellos de escritorio.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Applet Desktop</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Applet desktop</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Applets op het bureaublad</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Aplety pulpitu</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Elementos Gráficos do Ecrã</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Applety plochy</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Skrivbordsminiprogram</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Аплети на стільниці</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDesktop Appletsxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=liquidshell</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=liquidshell</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image> https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/liquidshell/liquidshell-light.png </image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>liquidshell</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="ca">liquidshell</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="ca-valencia">liquidshell</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="cs">liquidshell</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="de">liquidshell</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="en-GB">liquidshell</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="es">liquidshell</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="fi">liquidshell</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="gl">liquidshell</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="id">liquidshell</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="it">liquidshell</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="nl">liquidshell</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="pl">liquidshell</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="pt">liquidshell</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="sk">liquidshell</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="sv">Liquid-skal</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="uk">liquidshell</binary>
    <binary xml:lang="x-test">xxliquidshellxx</binary>
  </provides>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
